ticketdada.com 2013-04-05

# Ticket dada

TicektDADA’s privacy policy covers the collection and use of personal information that may be collected by TicektDADA anytime you interact with TicektDADA, such as when you visit our website, when you purchase TicektDADA products and services, or when you call/interact our sales or support associates, agents and affiliates. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at TicektDADA, and we go to great lengths to protect it.  

**Why we collect your personal information**  
Because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product and service announcements, updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about. 

If you do not want TicektDADA to communicate to you the TicektDADA news, updates and the latest information on products and services you may do so by editing your profile from "My Account" section and update your personal contact information and preferences accordingly on provision. 

**What information we collect**  
There are a number of situations in which your personal information may help us give you better service. For example, when registering at TicektDADA, when you're discussing a service issue on the phone with an associate, when downloading an item detail, participating in an online survey, registering/adding/selling/buying a product or service. At such times, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences; your credit card information and information about the TicektDADA products you own such as date of purchase etc; and information relating to a support or service issue. We collect information for market research purposes such as your occupation and where you use your computer to gain a better understanding of our customers and thus provide more valuable service. We also collect information regarding customer activities on our website, server, agent locations and on related websites. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our websites and Internet services are of most interest to them. 

The TicektDADA website, as well as TicektDADA services allows you to create an TicektDADA ID based on your personal information. This convenient service saves you time and allows for easier use of our web services. Here's how it works: You create a personal profile providing your name, phone number, email address, and in some cases your mailing address or a credit card number and choose a password and password hint (such as the month and day of your birth) for security. The system saves your information and assigns you a personal TicektDADA ID in many cases simply your phone number, because it's unique and easy to remember. The next time you wish to transact thru the Site or trade a new product or service, all you need to do is enter your TicektDADA ID and password; the system looks up the information it needs to assist you. In addition, if you update the information associated with your TicektDADA ID it will be available for all your transactions with TicektDADA globally. 

**When we disclose your information**  
TicektDADA takes your privacy very seriously. Be assured that TicektDADA does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers. To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with other Users of the Site, affiliates, agents and legal entities within the TicektDADA group globally who will safeguard it in accordance with TicektDADA’s privacy policy. There are also times when it may be advantageous for TicektDADA to make certain personal information about you available to companies that TicektDADA has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for TicektDADA to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with TicektDADA’s policies. Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to trade/transact at TicektDADA, have products/services delivered to you, receive customer service, provide us feedback to improve our products and services, or access certain services, requests, and content on the TicektDADA website. 

At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary. 

**How we protect your personal information**  
TicektDADA takes precautions including administrative, technical, and physical measures to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. 

You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers. 

**Integrity of your personal information**  
TicektDADA has safeguards in place to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date for the purposes for which it is used. Naturally, you always have the right to access and correct the personal information you have provided. You can help us ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate and complete. And you can request a copy of your personal information, your trade/transaction history, and your interactions with our customer service personnel by contacting us. 

**Cookies and other technologies**  
As is standard practice on many corporate websites, TicektDADA’s website uses "cookies" and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. We use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us. We use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our website, to make it even more rewarding as well as to study the effectiveness of our customer communications. For example, knowing your first name lets us welcome you with a greeting the next time you visit the Site. If, however, you prefer not to have such information stored on your computer, you may disable cookies on your computer as provided by your operating system. Please note that certain features of the TicektDADA website will not be available once cookies are disabled. 

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track user's movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. TicektDADA will not use the information collected to market directly to that person. 

In some of our email messages we use a "click-through URL" linked to content on the TicektDADA website. When a customer clicks one of these URLs, they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the email. In addition we use pixel tags tiny graphic images to tell us what parts of our website customers have visited or to measure the effectiveness of searches customers perform on our site. 

We store all of this information in a secure database located in and outside of India. We do not knowingly solicit personal information from minors or send them requests for personal information. TicektDADA’s website has links to the sites of other companies. TicektDADA is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies. TicektDADA may update its privacy policy from time to time. 

 Purchase Policy
